how did it happen that in the second year
как так получилось что на втором году
their Ukrainian drones are already attacking
сво украинские беспилотники уже атакуют
Russia to a depth of 800 km in the Leningrad
Россию на глубину 800 км в Ленинградскую
region of Tula and so
область Тулу и так
on
далее
Great I’m from the city of Khmelnitsk Where are you from
Прекрасно Я из города Хмельницке Вы
From the city of Khmelnitsk Are you from
откуда Из города Хмельницке Вы откуда
Russia Nizhny Novgorod region
Россия Нижегородская область
Nizhny Novgorod And what village specifically
Нижегородская А какой посёлок конкретно
Nizhny Novgorod what village specifically
нижегород какой посёлок конкретно
And why  village what city is a city I
А почему посёлок че города есть город Я
just don’t know which Arzamas I don’t know
не знаю просто какой Арзамас Я не знаю
Arzamas Maybe I know from Niro city
Арзамас Может я знаю из Ниро городско
city  Arzamas then everything is correct
городе Арзамас токо всё правильно
Arzamas Yes everything is correct I remember it
Арзамас Да всё правильно Я это помню ещё
was still you guessed it I just remember the song
было вы угадали Я просто помню песню
Just remember me the cab driver sent for
Просто пом меня извозчика отправил рза
me izm
меня изм
sent and I luggage of Russian culture
отпра бы и я поклади российской культуры
Soviet not Soviet but Soviet
Советской не Советской а Советской
Russian they scare you as not Russian
российской пугают вас неже не российский
was well he was included Yes  I understand, okay,
был ну он входил Да понятно ну ладно
this is the essence of the
этот Суть в
World Cup No, I was the first to ask, I was in the war, I was in
ЧМ Да нет Я первый спросил я войне я
the war, I understood, I’m listening to you, I’m ready
войне я понял Я вас слушаю готов
to listen, but I’m not asking, but I’m not
выслушать а я не спрашиваю а я не
I’m asking and don’t ask,
спрашиваю а не спрашивайте
just maybe you’re
только может вы какой-то
interested in why people from Ukraine in Russia are
интерес почему в Росси людям с украини
like people from Russia in Ukraine, we don’t have
как людям из России в Украине у нас нету
people from Russia, our borders are closed. No
людей из России у нас границы перекрыты
one from Russia
Никто из России сюда не
comes here, so that’s what I’m saying, that
приезжает так я про что и говорю что
people from Ukraine in  Russia meets en masse
люди с Украины в России массово
and people if they come from Russia
встречаются а люди если из России
to Ukraine They will be nch know not I
приедут в Украину Им будет нч знае не я
don’t know what chn is but they are unlikely to
не знаю что такое чн но они наврядли
come It’s just that our borders are closed
приедут Просто у нас закрыты грани
for you will not be able to come
для вы не сможете приехать
for  Ukrainian borders are open to Russia,
для украинцев границ открыты в Россию
and perhaps because Russia attacked
а возможно потому что Россия напала на
Ukraine and not Ukraine attacks
Украину а не Украина на
Russia. And the fact that Ukraine is bombing
Россию нет А то что Украина бомбит по
Russia is not a
территории России это как бы не служит
factor,
фактором
but it’s like a consequence of the fact that
что да это как бы следствие того что
Russia attacked Ukraine, so we are
Россия напала на Украину поэтому мы
bombing
бомбим
Russia. Clearly  in short, you this Listen, you
Россию Понятно короче вы этот Слушай
also can’t if it’s nonsense No no
тоже не можете если бред Не нет
interlocutor then I’ll listen you in some places no
собеседник то буду слушать вы местами
no nonsense Yes no I’m trying to ask a question
нете бред Да нет я пытаюсь вопрос задать
I understood the question from you I would like to
я понял от вас вопрос Хотелось бы
hear some way Get what
услышать какой-нибудь как-то Получи что
on  In the second year, Ukrainian
на втором году сво украинские
drones are already attacking Russia to a
беспилотники уже атакуют Россию на
depth of 800 km in the Leningrad region of
глубину 800 км в Ленинградскую область
Tula And so
Тулу И так
on, fine, I am
дальше прекрасно я
the manager of the Russian air defense, I will give you a
управляющий ПВО России я вам дам
competent answer 100% why Ukrainian
грамотный ответ 100% почему украинские
drones reach
беспилотники долетают
Russia, as expected, the
Росси ва как ждана
Leningrad
зать Дон зать Ленинградскую
region, of course, everyone has a
обла возникает конечно у всех возникает
question  and not specifically to Putin, after all, it’s not
вопрос и не конкретно к Путину ведь не
Putin who rules the
Путин рулит именно
air defense, but
ПВО
look at the responsibility. Well, in fact, about the
ответстве смотрите Ну да по факту об
fact, put any  a commercial
факту ставьте любую коммерческую
organization in any organization there is a
организацию в любой организации есть
general director, a commercial
генеральный директор коммерческий
director, then let's go deputy
директор дальше пошли заместитель
director Yes, the managers there of a
директора Да управляющие там регионом
region there a region here the same thing everything
там областью вот здесь то же самое всё
goes down Who controls the forces Well,
спускается вниз Кто управляет силам Ну
someone
кто-то
controls Who appoints the
управляет Кто назначает силы
air defense forces Well, the one who is above these is the one who
ПВО Ну тот кто выше этими тот кто
manages these forces  so this is who
заведует этими силами вот так вот кто
appoints him
его назначает
and who is even higher, and so along the chain
а кто ещё выше и так вот по цепочке
everything reaches the council,
доходит доходит всё до совета до в том
including the commander in chief, to Putin, yes, that
числе главнокомандующий до Путина да то
is, Putin is responsible for these personnel
есть Путин ответствен за эти кадровые
decisions, I’m right  I understand that these
решения я правильно понимаю что этих
military men are appointed by
военных назначает
Putin after him, as far as I understand, he
Путин за ним вот насколько я понимаю за
probably doesn’t have the last word. Well, it
ним наверное не последнее слово Ну как
seems to me that he is the Supreme
мне кажется конститу он верховный
Commander-in-Chief of the Constitution. Well,
главкома
let’s say Take the same
назначает Ну допустим Взять Ту же самую
America from them, too, it’s not the president who
Америку у них же тоже не президент всё
decides everything for them. Prim America isn’t here
решает у них ре Прим Америка не вот у
you We are talking specifically about Russia,
вас Мы же говорим конкретно про Россию
but your Senate doesn’t decide. We have,
да у вас сенат не решает У нас есть
wait, wait, in America there is a Senate.
подождите подождите в Америке есть сенат
We have a parliament, that is, Putin is not the
У нас есть парламент то есть Путин он не
only one at the helm, so I decided that
один руль такой раз такой я решил что
this is how it will be. This is how this is.
вот вот это будет Вот так А вот это
will be That's what the majority can say.
будет Вот так могут сказать большинство
Yes, listen, the majority can
Да Слушайте ему может большинство
tell him from parliament that you're wrong, as if
сказать из парламента что ты не прав как
the head of the air defense should be like this, it's not within the competence of
начальника ПВО это не в компетенции
parliament, it's within the competence of the Supreme
парламента это в компетенции верховного
Commander-in-Chief, your parliament doesn't
главнокомандующего у вас парламент не
have any Well, according to the Constitution,
имеет никакой Ну так по Конституции
there are services  who will lead the
поте о есть службы которые заведут
military military structure and there is also
военными военной структурой и там тоже
more than one person in charge. But it’s not
не один человек рулит Вот но не
the parliament that appoints the Supreme
парламент назначает Верховный
Commander-in-Chief Putin
главнокомандующий Путин
appoints wait, I’m saying what’s in
назначает подождите я говорю то что в
each  structure there is a certain council
каждой структуре есть определённый совет
of some kind
какойто
Kade primate together with Tim that’s all,
Каде примат ре совместно с Тим вот и всё
wait I don’t know who makes the
подождите я не знаю кто принимает
decision but according to the Constitution Yes, these
решение но по Конституции Да эти
powers are given to Putin More precisely, not to
полномочия отданы Путину Точнее не
Putin, but to the President of the Russian Federation,
Путину а Президенту Российской Федерации
who is now
которым сейчас является
Putin Yes, this is how it turns out If he is
Путин Да так получается Если он несёт
responsible for these personnel  decisions,
ответственность за эти кадровые решения
he is responsible for the beginning of his
он несёт ответственность за начало сво
it turns out that when they are now bombing
получается что когда сейчас бомбят
Belgorod,
Белгород
Leningrad region, Tula region,
Ленинградскую область тульскую область
Oryol, Smolensk, Yes,
орловскую Смоленскую Да несёт за это всё
in the end,
в конце концов Путин ко концов
Putin bears the responsibility for it all.  Well, damn it, in fact,
Путин Ну блин по факту наверное Может
maybe yes, but the essence is what do you want? The essence is
быть и да Но суть то в чём Что вы хотите
what, yes, that is, look
при Суть в чём да то есть смотрите
Why do
Почему
n’t people ask Putin how it
люди не спросят у Путина как так
happened that we undertook to defend the
получилось что мы взялись защищать
Donbass now and didn’t protect the Donbass
Донбасс теперь и Донбасс не защитили Да
And yet our people suffer  regions, in
и ещё и страдают наши регионы
fact, you know what the answer to this
на самом деле знаете какой ответ на этот
question is. If we take the fact that Russia is
вопрос Если взять по факту Россия - это
Russia, Ukraine is Ukraine, and let’s say
Россия Украина - это Украина и допустим
we push our heads purely against Russia and
вот лбами столкнуть чисто вот Россию
Ukraine, well, without external interference, well,
Украину ну без внешнего вмешательства ну
in fact, it would be like Ukraine would be here.
по факту как бы тут Украина будет Вот
Here  Russia will be here like this and
здесь Россия будет вот здесь вот так а
how does it turn out that Ukraine is
так как получается что Украину Ну
being sponsored by Western countries Well, that’s right
спонсирует страны запада Ну правильно Да
Yes yes or no Yes yes that’s cool
да или нет Да да это классно
no What did I say that’s so funny for
вот нет Что я такого смешного сказал для
you not I Radu not you said Ukraine
вас не я Раду не вы сказали Украину
is sponsored by Western countries It’s not funny
спонсирует страны запада Это не смешно
it’s
это
joyful  And what are you rejoicing about? Are you
радостно А вы А что вы радуетесь вы
rejoicing at what’s happening now? Well,
радуетесь то что сейчас происходит Ну
look at the EU. You said, if you take it,
смотри ЕС Вы же сказали если взять толь
look, if you take Ukraine and Russia,
смотрите если взять Украину и Россию да
and push their heads together without the support of the West,
и столкнуть лбами без поддержки Запада
then there will be Ukraine, here’s Russia, you
вот будет Украина вот Россия вы это
showed it, I showed it  I understand I’m
показали я это понимаю Мне это
scared Yes, you said that Well, since
страшно Да вы сказали что Ну так как
Western countries are helping Ukraine and I
Украине помогают страны запада и у меня
immediately feel warm in my soul, I say yes,
сразу тепло в душе я та да
help But you’re talking about Well, yes, Well,
помогай А вот вы про Ну это да Ну
you probably deserved, well, this support,
наверное вы заслужили э ну эту поддержку
maybe that’s why I’m saying that you
возможно вот поэтому вот я и говорю что
don’t  if there had been no support from the West, there were no bombs
не будь поддержки Запада не было бамб и
in Leningrad either. I don’t agree. If there had
по Ленинграде Согласен не Если бы не
been no support from the West, you would have taken
было поддержки Запада вы бы ки взяли за
two or three maximum in 2 days. Yes, no one
2 дня два-три максимум Да это никто не
argues there was no support from the West, all
спорит не было поддержки Запада всё
Ukraine and the vyb were already near Poland, but
Украина и выб уже стояли под Польшей но
support from the West is support from the
поддержка Запада есть поддержка
West are you lucky or why I
Запада вам это вам это повезло или зас Я
don’t know what you did that they
не знаю вот что вы такое сделали что вам
started helping you like that Well I also don’t know
стали так помогать Хорошо я тоже не знаю
what you did young man
что вы сделали такого молодой человек
I don’t know I think maybe we
вот не знаю я думаю что может мы
showed At first they thought it was Russia
показали Сначала думали что вот Россия
will take and take over Ukraine, and Ukraine
возьмёт и захватит Украину а Украина
took it and gave Russia a punch in the teeth and everyone thinks,
взяла дала России по зубам и все думают
listen,
слушай
you can help. Well done, they gave it to the teeth. Well done,
можно помогать Ну молодцы дали по зубам
yes, and now they are giving us more
Молодцы что ж да А теперь нам всё больше
and more, now I’ll say this. I just
и больше дают тепер я скажу так Я просто
remember my emotions when I first
помню свои эмоции когда первый раз
flew to Russia.  In the Belgorod
прилетела по Белгородской
region in Belgorod, we dropped videos like they
области в Белгород у нас видео типа
dropped videos like
скидывали скидывали типа видео как в
explosions in Belgorod, I was really happy, I was
Белгороде взрывы я реально радовался я
really happy that there
реально радовался что по территории
were attacks on the territory of Russia, then
России идут удары тогда
everyone saw that there was nothing, they started
все посмотрели что ничего нету начали
bombing, then now it’s already flying for the
бомбить дальше теперь уже долетает
second year since it will be, yes, on February 24,
второй год с будет вот да 24 февраля
Leningradskaya is flying  region 800 km
долетает Ленинградская область 800 км
successfully terminal on the Baltic Sea
успешно терминал на Балтийском море
vli VTU plant that makes shells
вли вту завод который панцири делает впи
in Orel something was thrashed in Smolensk just in general  no
в Орле что-то лупили в Смоленске вобще
one remembers every
никто не вспоминает каждый
day I somehow
день У меня как-то
inspire more and more
воодушевить всё больше и больше делать
strikes on the territory of the Russian
ударов по территории Российской
Federation, so what city are you from, I
Федерации так вот вы с какого города
’ll remind you, and Arzamas Well, in my opinion, don’t
напомню а Арзамас Ну туда по-моему не
fly there, the region is one This is Prilepin like
долетай области едино Это прилепина типа
yes they blew up blew up what blew up Well,
да взорвали взорвали чего взорвали Ну
Prilepin’s propagandist  blew up
пропагандиста прилепина взорвали
[music]
[музыка]
blew up blown up but no, well,
подорвали подорвали но не ну
they flew alive, I
летели живой
stayed at the beginning I don’t know, I don’t know how the Lich didn’t
остался нач не знаю я как бы Лич не
touch the pine
трогал сосне
tree in the sense of it  he’s walking Why have they
висе в смыс так он же ходит Почему
already sewed
пришили уже
something to what you’re getting at, I’m just seeing
что-то к чему клоните я просто смотрю
that with every month Ukraine
что с каждым месяцем со Украина
is increasing and increasing its military
наращивает и наращивает свой военный
potential, we were given highmore sons who are
потенциал нам дали хаймор сы которые
already working, long-range missiles
работают уже вот дальнобойные ракеты
Storm Shadow scalp that are hitting
Шторм Shadow скальп которые бьют по
Crimea Yes, no problem, they give, I don’t know, they give
Крыму Да без проблем дают не знаю дают
Or we ourselves make these drones
Или мы сами делаем вот эти беспилотники
that attack the Leningrad region and
которые лупят по Ленинградской области и
so on, that is, Ukraine is expanding the
так дальше то есть Украина расширяет
geography of strikes, what to counter
географию ударов что противопоставить
this with Russia, I don’t know, they told me before
этому Россия я не знаю раньше мне
that in my country there is no war,
говорили что у меня в стране войны не
my bombs, missiles are not coming,
идт у меня бомбы ракеты не прилетают
now it turns out they are coming from
теперь оказывается прилетают у
you. Well, they are flying in. And they are flying to us, and
вас Ну и прилетают И вам прилетают нам и
so they were flying to us, well, they were flying to us, we have
так прилетали ну нам прилетали мы
resigned ourselves because we were attacked. It’s clear.
смирились потому что На нас напали
Why did they attack you, more precisely to you?
Понятно А вам почему напали точнее вам
Why is
Почему
it flying in the sense  you resigned yourself
прилетает в смысле вы смирились вам же
there, they gave you the Patriots' shell, you
там панцире Патриотов надавали вы
resigned
смирились вы
yourself, you knocked down, we understand not absolutely, look at
сби мы понимаем не абсолю смотри у
us, look at us, we understand Yes, that’s part  there
на смотри у нас мы понимаем Да что часть
will be arrivals, everyone understands, and when there is an
прилётов будет все понимают и когда есть
arrival and no one shouts, everyone
прилёт и никто не кричит прилёт все
understands that Russia is attacking with enormous
понимают Да что Россия атакует огромным
potential. Yes, and there will be arrivals, everyone
потенциалом Да и прилёты будут все с
understands this, everyone goes to shelters and so on.
этим понимают все в укрытия и так дальше
Yes, but I think that the residents of the Leningrad
Да но я думаю что жители Ленинградской
region of Tula were not ready for such
области Тульской были не готовы к такому
a turn  what will fly over
повороту сво что будет прилетать по
them and no one knew what would actually happen next
ним а никто не знал что дальше будет на
Well, really no one knew Yeah,
самом деле Ну реально никто не знал Угу
but are you ready, for example, for a military
а готовы вы например к военному
clash between NATO countries,
столкновению странами НАТО
nomin Am I ready or not Yeah, well, I would
номина Я готов или нет Угу Ну мне бы не
I wouldn’t like it I wouldn’t want it
хотелось мне бы не хотелось этого
of course Well, you don’t know how to
конечно Ну вот вы же не знаете как
continue But it can develop further
дальше Бут развиваться может дальше ещё
Russia Finland will attack
Россия Финляндия нападёт
correctly so that’s why no one No, that’s
правильно поэтому поэтому никто Нет это
not true that’s why no one knew how
неправда поэтому никто не знал чем всё
this whole thing would turn out about the beginning with so Well
это дело обернётся о начале с поэтому Ну
damn, what we have is what we have  someone is in the plus
блин что имеем то имеем кто-то в плюсе
someone is in the minus it was always
кто-то в минусе это всегда это было
like that maybe it’s time to
может как бы ту может уже пора тогда
finish your time In short, it somehow
заканчивайте свой раз Короче оно как-то
went wrong
пошло не так
Why finish Well because
Почему заканчивать Ну потому что с
every year with every month and day more
каждым годом с каждым месяцем и днём всё
and more  more Russians turn out yes
больше и больше россиян получается
Well, it turns out you agree now
дае Ну получается Вы согласны сейчас
legitimize your on
законите сво на
those on those advances that everyone
тех на тех продвижения что все
has stopped no no that you are leaving
остановились не нет что вы выходите с
the territory of Ukraine on the border of the ninety-
территории Украины на границе девяносто
first year and that’s it Well otherwise Otherwise we will
первого года и всё Ну ина Иначе мы будем
continue to hit the territory of the Russian
и дальше бить по территории Российской
Federation and how will you stop  strikes on the
Федерации а как вы Остановите удары по
territory of the Russian Federation, the
территории Российской Федерации
territory of the Russian Federation,
территории Российской Федерации так так
just like you won’t stop on the
же никак Как и вы не Остановите по
territory of Ukraine. That is, it turns out
территории Украины То есть получается
that Putin wants the
что Путин Да хочет чтобы и дальше
Russian Federation to continue to be bombed.
бомбили Российскую Федерацию Российскую
Federation Well, about this, he wants, he doesn’t
Федерацию А ну на насчёт этого хочет не
want, I don’t know, well, damn it. What is it, that
хочет не знаю вот ну блин Что есть то
is, you want the Russians to be bombed further?
есть вы хотите чтобы дальше бомбили
You know, you really do
россий знае Вы знаете Вы на самом деле
n’t have any illusions that
особо иллюзии не питайте то что у вас с
some kind of drone flew in from Ukraine 800 km away
Украины 800 км прилетел там какой-то
and  hit Leningrad, this is
беспилотник и ударил по ленинграду это
100%
100%
120% It won’t reach from Ukraine But this is a Fact,
120% С Украины он не долетит Но это Факт
there are such
есть такие
people Well, there are such people who simply
люди Ну есть такие люди которые просто
live on the territory of Russia and that’s
проживают на территории России и вот и
all Well, this is my opinion personally correct  I
всё Ну это моё мнение лично правильно
understand in simple words a
понимаю простыми сло простыми словами
saboteur is called perhaps the
Диверсант называется возможно те же
same perhaps the same refugees
самые возможно те же самые беженцы
who came from the territory of Ukraine Well,
которые приехали с территории Украины Ну
under the guise of refugees But in fact perhaps
под видом беженцев А по факту возможно
saboteurs, I understand correctly that these
Диверсанты я правильно понимаю что эти
saboteurs are
Диверсанты
somewhere very
гдето теро
huge
огромный
collecting collecting collecting And what is
собирают собирают собирают А что вас в
so surprising about this for you?  the drone
этом такого удивляет для беспилотника
needs some kind of extra nanotechnology or
нужны какие-то сверх нанотехнологии что
something, or factory passages, I
ли или завода проходы я правильно
understand correctly that at home they
понимаю что в домашних условиях они
assemble a drone that
собирают беспилотник который абсолютно
absolutely bypasses these RBs Yes, and it arrives
точно обходит эти РБ Да и прилетает
exactly according to
точно по
coordinates We have a problem ordering
координатам У нас есть проблема заказать
goods from China to Russia. I just don’t know
товар из Китая в Россию Я просто не знаю
if this can be ordered from China.
ли из Китая можно такое за
Where do they also
можно заказать А взрывчатку где они тоже
order explosives? What explosives are also for these
заказы чего взрывчатку тоже для этих
drones? They order from China.
беспилотников они из Китая заказывают
They order from China. Well,
они из Китая заказывают Ну нач
the explosives start somewhere here  they are mining damn you
взрывчатки где-то здесь добывают блин вы
think there is no smuggling in your country
думаете контрабанды нету в вашей стране
and in our country I don’t understand, look
и в нашей стране я не понимаю смотрите
now there is a war and the FSB, someone with a tray from the
сейчас идёт Война и ФСБ кто-то подносом
FSB is buying huge drones from China
ФСБ массово из Китая покупает огромные
somewhere, mining a bunch of explosions
беспилотники где-то добывает куча взрыв
day somewhere you fly somewhere every day
день куда-то тя каждый день куда-то
They fly somewhere every day who
летят Они каждый день куда летят кто
yesterday look yesterday they flew to St. Petersburg and
вчера смотри вчера летели в Питер и в
Bryansk Yes today they flew Tula Peter and
Брянск Да сегодня летели Тула Питер э
Orel and Smolensk the previous one actually
Орёл и Смоленск предыдущий ещё реально
flies every time and when the previous ones
летает каждый раз а когда предыдущие
were when the previous ones every week
были когда предыдущие каждую неделю
really  not uh almost every day Yes
реально не вот э почти каждый день Да
every day yes look Take news
каждый день да смотри Возьмите новости
like the Ukrainian BP in
типа украинский БП по
fact the question
факту вопрос К компетентным органам
should be asked to the competent authorities and not to people usually It’s
нужно задавать а не к людям обычно
just incomprehensible such a large geography of
Просто непонятно такая большая география
saboteurs and in  Krasnodar Territory Yes, it
диверсантов и в Краснодарском крае Да
turns out that in the Rostov region in the
выходит и в Ростовской области в
Bryansk Leningrad region, that is, all over
Брянской Ленинградской то есть по всей
Russia, there are some Saboteurs where I can’t do
России какие-то Диверсанты где Я не могу
this without laughing, I couldn’t help but
это без ржаки не смог не
laugh, they actually take some spare parts from China, and
заржать берут с Китая какие-то запчасти
it’s not like this is a
реально причём это же не то что это
ready-made wing on the
готовое крыло
cob where  -they find it in such
початку где-то находят в таких
quantities and launch it and Listen, you
количествах и запускают и Слушай вот зна
know, I have
знаешь у меня
people from Ukraine for some reason. I don’t know why, I do
вот народ из Украины почему-то Я не знаю
n’t know why, I have people from
почему вот не знаю почему у меня из
your head doesn’t go away, like, well, seriously,
головы не уходит вы как вот ну серьёзно
you’ll get gold out of the dead Well,
Вы из мёртвого достанете золото Ну вот
that’s my word of honor, that’s why Well, damn, there are
вот Честное слово поэтому Ну блин
saboteurs 100%, that’s how
Диверсанты есть 100% вот а как как всё
it all happens, they’re not them, but
это происходит они не они но 800 км
a drone can fly 800 km, well, well, why would it be
беспилотник пролететь ну Ну как бы б
Well, Russian, so before  2000 km
почему Ну российский так до 2000 км
can fly maybe Well, maybe Yes, I’m
может лететь может ть Ну может быть Да я
incompetent in this Well, about Well, I don’t know,
в этом некомпетентен Ну про Ну не знаю
it seems to me Although you know, to be honest,
мне кажется Хотя знаете вот честно
even the version with saboteurs  I'm happy with
говоря меня даже версия с диверсантами
it, but saboteurs are not saboteurs. The point is that Ukraine is somehow organizing the bombing of Russian cities. China will then supply us with these spare parts for our saboteurs in Russia;  su
раз Но на самом деле Вы зря так это су
grin Well, because well, you find it
ухмылка относитесь Ну потому что ну Вам
funny to some people from Ukraine, it’s far
смешно некоторым людям из Украины далеко
from funny
не смешно
when it flies across the territory of Russia
когда прилетает по территории России
Why Because we understand that
Почему Потому что мы понимаем что
Ukraine gives an answer Dutt and  the fact that
Украина даёт ответку Датт а то что
it flies across the territory of Ukraine not from But
прилетает по территории Украины не с А
across the territory through the territory of Ukraine and
по территории по территории Украины и
so it flies, that’s the trick, you know,
так прилетает в том-то и фишка понимаешь
on the territory of Ukraine what I’m talking about, that
по территории украи про что я говорю то
is, it flew across Russia, you’re laughing, but it
есть по России прилетела вы смеётесь а
flew into the territory of Ukraine, according to Well, it’s
територи Украины прилетела смете Ну да
logical that this is where the laughter disappeared  he
логично такое куда смех пропал сразу он
didn’t appear right away Well, look when he flies
не появлялся Ну смотри когда прилетает
over us We don’t laugh, we didn’t laugh,
по нам Мы не смеёмся мы не смеялись вы
you’re sitting now, you’re laughing
сечас вы сейчас сидите смеётесь у вас не
wrong, I’m laughing at what’s coming  for you
так я смеюсь что прилетает по вам ещё
again, look
раз смотри
both of you, look first for the first few months it
обя смотри сначала первые месяцы с по
came to us, we didn’t laugh, then it
нам прилетало мы не смеялись потом
started to fly around Belgorod, we started
начало прилетать по Белгороду мы начали
laughing, it started to fly around Moscow,
смеяться начало прилетать по Москве по
we laughed, that is, we laugh Well, that’s
мы смеялись то есть мы смеёмся Ну это
logical Look, when they play football, when
логично Смотри когда футбол играют когда
they score a goal on your team, you don’t
забивают гол твоей команде ты не
you laugh When yours scores you laugh
смеёшься Когда твоя забивает ты смеёшься
like that and then when Melis flies into my city
так и тут когда прилетает в мой город
I honestly don’t laugh, I say
Мелис Я честно не смеюсь я говорю
Russian terrorists shelled my
российские террористы обстреляли Мой
city  when Ukraine launched something or
город когда Украина запустил что-то или
Saboteurs Saboteurs I apologize the
Диверсанты Диверсанты извиняюсь
territory of the Russian Federation
территории Российской Федерации
flies to Leningrad I'm
прилетает в Ленинград Я
like this I'm happy I'm happy honor You see
такой Я радуюсь Я радуюсь чест Видите
See this is equivalent to let's say if
Видите это равносильно допустим вот если
we take a comparison about football again, in football we have the World Cup there The
нас же в футболе есть там чемпионат мира
European Championship is the Champions League
Чемпионат Европы есть Лига Чемпионов
there is a Europa League, a conference league. So
есть Лига Европы лига конференций Вот и
in the conference league, sometimes
в лига конференции бывает сталкиваются
teams collide, well, take for example Well, from the
команды ну к примеру взять Ну из
Israeli League, let’s say some kind of poppy league,
израильской допустим Лиги какой-нибудь
so he plays with  Real Madrid, for example,
вот и он играет с Реал Мадрид к примеру
that's when Maccabi scores against Real Madrid
вот когда Маккаби забивает Реал Мадриду
They're all happy Well done, they scored,
Вот они все радуются Молодцы забили вот
but Real Madrid in fact still knows
а Реал Мадрид по факту всё равно знает
that the outcome will be logical Well,
что ну исход то он будет закономерен Вот
they scored here tomorrow they'll score They're 10 and they'll
ну забили здесь завтра забьют Им 10 и
kind of laugh now then
как бы ну посмеются сейчас потом всё
anyway Booth  Well, somehow,
равно Бут Да ну как-то
look at this, it’s Ukraine and re
смотрите это Украина а ре
Madrid, if we look if it’s
Мадрид если если мы смотрим если бы это
just Ukraine and Russia were playing, but you
просто Украина и Россия играла но вы же
understand that the best players in the world play for Ukraine,
понимаете что за Украину играют лучшие
USA, Britain  France
США Британия Германия Франция Япония
strength,
экономический по экономической силе
the Balts are not in business or are they in
начинаю прибалты не при делах что ли при
business? Well, I say, I first Now the
делах Ну я же говорю я сначала Сейчас
strong players are further than the smaller
сильных игроков дальше более меньших
players, I  It’s just more economical,
игроков я по экономиче просто получается
so we’ve
так
agreed that I can still
что договорили я могу там ещё очень
eat a lot there, and even a lot of it.
много есть да е очень ного А можете
Can you name which players play for you?
можете назвать какие игроки за вас
It’s
играют вот
interesting that we compared the composition of the
интересно что мы сравнили состав
teams, so that’s the whole point; Real
команд так в этом есть вся суть вот Реал
Madrid is the only one like that, and that’s
Мадрид он один-единственный такой и там
it  All the best players from one country play at once.
вот играют все лучшие сразу из одной
But in your club they play a
страны А вот в вашем клубе играют везде
little bit everywhere, so how can you tell the composition of
по чуть-чуть вот как бы лу можете состав
your team
своей команды
Korea correctly Iran Eritrea
рассказать Корея правильно Иран эритрея
Well, you can name Who is on your team
Да ну можете назвать Кто в вашу команду
and why should I name it I have
входит а зачем мне называть У меня есть
I’m just interested  Here  look,
мне интересно просто вот смотрите вот
since you started football there Maccabi there or
раз футбол вы начали там Маккаби там или
someone, I said the composition of our team
ктото вот я состав нашей команды сказал
No, I said So you started about Maccabi
Не ну я сказал Вот вы начали про макаби
And so on Yes, here I am the composition of our
И так дальше Да вот я состав нашей
team Rask I’m interested in what
команды раска мне интересно у вас какие
players you have announced on the
заявленные игроки на
field we have our Russians declared  so
поле у нас заявлены наши российские так
Nuri North Korea Dat to you SD
Нури Северная Корея Дат вам СД
may be
может быть
Dat on your field Russia North Korea
Дат у вас на поле Россия Северная Корея
Who
Кто
else Why do we need someone else
ещё А зачем нам кого-то ещё
Why Seriously Why do we need someone else
Зачем Ну серьёзно Зачем нам кого-то ещё
Think about
Подумайте у вас
it, it’s
сме
plausible not for me Well let
правдоподобный не пропо мне Хорошо пусть
me  plausible I'm
мне правдоподобный Я
laughing the essence is what In the end The essence is that
ржу суть то в чём В итоге Суть в том что
Russians who are Russians that is the essence
русские кто русские вот в чём суть
Russian essence yes yes what does this mean
русский суть да да а что это означает
Russian essence Well the essence is that Russian is
русский суть Ну в том суть что русский
the essence
суть
Russia we have a proverb the meaning is Yes
Россия вот у нас пословица смыс это Да
this is a Ukrainian folk proverb  Well,
это это украинская народная пословица Ну
it’s difficult to convey, it’s an untranslatable
её трудно передать это непереводимая
idiom. Yes, that’s the point:
идиома Да что в том и суть что
Russia. Well, if there is such a thing, then there are Handsome
росия Ну если есть такой Значит есть
Men.
Красавцы Давайте на на этой на этой идём
not an
и закончим А что так всё сливай не не
interesting question Let's have another
есть интересный вопрос Давайте ещё
question I'll play football with you
вопрос я с вами ещё футбол поиграю
Let's have another question
Давайте ещё какой-то вопрос
No So you didn't ask me anything
есть нет Так вы же мне ничего не задали
I asked you a question who plays for you
Я вам задал вопрос кто за вас играет
Russia and North Korea and you merged
Россия и Северная Корея и вы слились
Korea merged no And I asked you  question
Корея слились нет А я вам задал вопрос
Why Russia Well, nothing happens to Ukrainians in Russia,
Почему Россия Ну украинцы в России
but for Russian Russians in
ничего не бывает а российским русским в
Ukraine Yes, well, I could answer Yes
Украине Да хорошо може бы отвечу Да
because because Russia is a country Yes,
потому что потому что Россия страна Да
it lets in all the Ukrainian
она пускает туда всех украинских
saboteurs who launch  from that
диверсантов которые запускают с той
territory its own drones, and Ukraine
территории свои э беспилотники а Украина
doesn’t want to let Russian citizens into its
не хочет пускать граждан России на свою
territory so that there are no saboteurs
территорию чтобы не было диверсантов
so that they don’t launch drones here.
чтобы они не запускали тут беспилотники
Listen, the question is this: in
Слушайте а вопрос такой ещё вот вы в
the end, what will you pay for later?
итоге чем расплачиваться будете потом
I’m just
просто мне
wondering what kind of economy it is necessary to have so
интересно како Какой нужно это иметь
that later  this whole thing, that
хозяйство чтобы потом всё это дело то
is, wait, I understand correctly that you
есть подожди я правильно понимаю что вы
will capture us and we have switched to you. I
нас захватите а мы на ты перешли Я
say, I understood correctly that you will
говорю я правильно понял что вы нас
capture us, yes, and we will have to
захватите да И нам придётся
pay, so if you capture us,
расплачиваться так если вы нас захватите
we will no longer have to pay anything
нам уже не придётся ничем расплачиваться
you will capture us than to pay us
вы нас захватите чем расплачиваться нас
capture So your policy is such that
захвати Так у вас же политика такая что
you are naked now and everything is so if we
вы нас сейчас наг и всё так если мы вас
nan you then you will pay and not
нанм то вы будете расплачиваться а не
correctly you will pay
правильно вы будете расплачиваться
correctly sry we will not ra any any
правильно сри мы не будем ра любом любом
in any races we are not paying in  in any
в любом рас мы не расплачиваемся в любом
case, if you captured us,
раскладе Если вы нас захватили нас уже
we won’t have to pay, you
нам не придётся расплачиваться вы нас
captured us and that’s it. And if we kick you out,
захватили и всё и А если мы вас выгоним
you will pay, everything is
вы будете расплачиваться всё просто
simple, that is, and you admit
просто то есть а вы допускаете такой
that Ukraine will not  will exist
момент что Украина не будет существовать
Well or Ukraine Yes for example if yes If
Ну или Украина Да например если да Если
now Yes for example on our field all the
сейчас Да например на нашем поле все
players USA Canada Australia France
игроки США Канада Австралия Франция
Germany Britain will leave the field Yes and
Германия Британия уйдут с поля Да и
only our Ukrainian goalkeeper will remain
останется только наш вратарь украинский
Yes well then yes Then we will lose you will score
Да ну тогда да Тогда мы проиграем вы
all the goals quickly and win Yes
забьём все голы быстро и выиграете Да
that’s it  this could be Yes, but something
вот такое может быть Да но что-то мне
seems to me, you know, the dynamics of the game on the playing
кажется знаете динамика игры на игровом
field are somehow changing not in the direction of the
поле как-то меняется не в сторону
Russian Federation in the direction of the
Российской Федерации в сторону
Russian Federation
Российской Федерации
Depending on who it is, well how For whom you
Смотря для кого как ну как Для кого
look, Russia received Unreal
смотрите Россия получила Нереальных
stars  near Kiev
звездюлей под Киевом
she fled in the Kharkov region she received a
убежала в Харьковской области получила
star and fled in Kherson she received a
звезде и убежала в Херсоне получила
star She escaped And now Ukraine has killed the
звезде Убежала А теперь Украина убила
offensive potential of the Russian
наступательный потенциал Российской
Federation The Russian Federation is
Федерации Российская Федерация за
fighting for some individual villages,
какие-то там отдельные сёла борется всё
it can no longer lay claim to any city
она ни за какой город уже не может
and Ukraine is now beginning
претендовать а Украина начинает теперь
to increase military production  and Peter
наращивать военное производство и Питер
Well, let’s not
Ну не будем так уж
say it so directly, please tell us everything about
прямо скажите пожалуйста вот всё про
some kind of counter-offensive, they said that there was
какой-то контрнаступ там говорили что
something
что-то
there. The thing is that I’m
там Дело в том
explaining, see our  military
что объясняю смотрите наше военное
command Yes, our military
командование Да наше военное
command does not announce its plans to
командование свои планы не объявляет
anyone, the real ones. It’s logical for us and for you,
никому настоящие Ни нам ни вам это же
yes, there is a media that
логично правда да есть медийка которая
Well, why because they
Ну почему потому что они военные планы
never tell you the plan of
никогда вам не рассказывают план
attack and so Dasha is
наступления и так Даше
true You ask me why
правда Здра меня спрашиваете Почему у
our air defense works like that.  Yes, it’s not like that. I’m
нас ПВО так работа Да не так Я вам
explaining to you. Yes, look, we
объясняю Да что смотрите
both look,
наме обя обю смотрите для вас
information about the counterattack is being dropped for you. Yes, so
скидывается информация про контрнаступ
that you keep all your forces in that
Да чтоб вы все свои силы держали на том
direction. Yes, and during this time you have not
направлении Да и за это время вы не
advanced anywhere, that is, Ukraine
продвинулись никуда то есть Украина
This
выиграла этим
media gained time to deliver
медийным время для того чтобы поставить
its weapons to its factories and now it is
своё вооружение свои заводы иве теперь
unhindered across the territory of the
беспрепятственно по территории
Russian Federation and you know what’s most
Российской Федерации и знаете что самое
interesting? Look, the joke is that when
интересное Да смотрите прикол что когда
Russia began its offensive, it said now we will
Россия начала сво она говорила сейчас мы
capture Kiev and Lviv, we will reach the English Channel
захватим Киев и Львов дойдём до Ла Манша
And now Russia says where the offensive is
А теперь Россия говорит где наступление
Ukraine, that is, Russia no longer thinks, you,
Украины то есть Россия уже не думает вы
as a Russian, have come to terms with the fact that it is
как россиянин смирились тем что
not Russia that is attacking,
наступает не Россия
really no, wait, say Kai,
правда нет подождите е Говорите Кай
counterattack, go If you are talking about
контрнаступ поди Если вы говорите про
counterattack  read you are talking about the
контрнаступ чит вы говорите про
offensive of
наступление
Ukraine, dear, you can
Украины уважаемы вы можете
listen
послушать
there is So I answer th listen it was
есть Так я отвечаю го послушать это было
so rapier that well, we were waiting for
настолько рапире что ну мы ждали
some kind of waiting to move Look at
какой-то ждали двигаться Вот смотри за
last
прошлый
year you can listen I told you We were
год можете послушать Я же сказал Мы
waiting for Kai to happen
ждали что будет Кай
and in the
а в
end this is what it’s like  it turned out that is, you
итоге вот так вот получилось то есть Вы
got it You were waiting for
получили Вы ждали и
you too Why Well, because look
вас Почему Ну потому что смотри потому
because you were waiting for a counterattack and in reality
что Вы ждали контрнаступ и в реальности
you haven’t advanced anywhere in a year
вы за год никуда не продвинулись
so it turns out well for you yes yes but as a
так получается ну для вас да да но в
result you haven’t advanced Who
результате вы не продвинулись Кто
you won by counting you haven’t
выиграл вы на считаете вы не
advanced so that’s what I’m talking about It’s
продвинулись так я про что и говорю Вот
not just that I have it in my head
не просто так у меня в голове крутится
that you
что вы
look Explain to me in a year the second army of
смотри Объясни мне за год вторая армия
the world that’s how much Russia Yes has advanced
мира вот сколько Россия Да продвинулась
and where In what directions How many
и где На каких направлениях На сколько
kilometers in a year a year well on  many
километров за год год ну на много
kilometers have pushed you where Yes where have you
километров отжали вас где Да где вы за
advanced in a year in what territories
год продвинулись на каких территориях На
How much ki I am with a tape measure I am with a tape measure I am with a
сколько ки я с рулеткой я с рулеткой я с
tape measure in your territory in ours it’s
рулеткой по вашей территории по нашей
already dumb Well, tell me yes Tell me  what
уже неме Ну скажите да Скажите какие
territories have you captured in a year, here is
территории вы захватили за год вот 2023
2023, well, wait, wait, wait, that’s
год ну подождите подождите подождите вот
how your football teams
так так как у вас футбольные команды
are made up of only
собраны исключительно
foreign players, that’s why, maybe
легионеров вот поэтому поэтому возможно
plans will have to be shifted a little, but
планы немножко придётся сдвинуть но
later, here’s a simple
попозже вот сжи простой
question, that’s simple. You must also
вопрос вот просто Вы должны тоже
understand the potential of Russia, what will we allow
понимать потенциал России что допустим
for you  a bunch of foreign players are playing against an
за вас куча легионеров играет против
ordinary team without foreign players, so it
обычной команды без легионеров вот и
turns out
получается
that they
что об
captured in 202 for a whole year and where they
захвати за 202 год за целый год да где
advanced Which city was captured Which
продвинулась Какой город захватила Какое
village region for a whole
село область за целый
year to you  Bakhmut is not enough Marinka is not enough Yes
год Вам бахмута мало Маринки мало Да
Bakhmut Bakhmut is still the result of the Code yes
бахмут бахмут это ещё результат Кода да
Well Bakhmut is there at a 7 km
Ну бахмут это там 7 км
pace said that VM e poisoning with us
шагу сказал что ВМ е отрава зах у нас
began in VM year
сво началось в ВМ году так
and at the end of the second year yes they stormed
и в конце д второго года да штурмовали
Bakhmut in the spring
бахмут ве весной
Bakhmut was repulsed Good Everything is Bakhmut  Come on,
бахмут был отбит Хорошо Всё бахмут Давай
bakhmut is 10 km from the front line. That
бахмут - это 10 км от линии фронта То
is, you have advanced 10 km. Yes, that’s
есть вы за продвинулись за 10 км Да я
what I’m talking about, so I’m telling you A  you
про что и говорю вот я вам называю А вы
're trying to me, I'm right now
пытаетесь меня я сейчас прямо Смотри я
Look, I'm turning on the map right now, look at
включаю сейчас прям карту смотрите
Bakhmut, let's Bakhmut, so here's Bakhmut, it's from the
бахмут давай бахмут так вот бахмут он от
invasion line, here Meriem has a
линии вторжения вот Мерием есть
measurement from the invasion line, it's 7 km Yes, the
измерение от линии вторжения он 7 км Да
length of Bakhmut itself is
длина самого бахмута
clear from the extreme point of
сесс очистить от крайней точки
Bakhmut to the other edge, 10 km long
бахмута так до другой край 10 км длина
bakhmuta and the width at the greatest
бахмута а ширина в наибольшей
point is 8 km
точке 8 км
in a year. You captured a piece of land 10 km
за го Вы захватили кусочек земли 10 км
by 8 km. That is, that’s all you got
на 8 км То есть это всё что вы получили
in
за
a year, no, that’s just a specific case  in another
год нет это просто конкретный случай ещ
specific
конкретный
case, what I know is what I know for
случа то что я знаю то что я знаю на
sure, wait for me, wait, you didn’t
дем каже подожди мне каже подожди ты не
answer, so I’m really saying,
ответил вот я реально говорю Да
why didn’t you answer? Dawa, you didn’t answer
что Вы не ответили Дава Вы не ответили
that Russia, that it’s SG for 202, that
что Россия что она СГ тить за 202 год То
is, you named some-  then a piece of land
есть вы назвали какой-то кусочек земли
10M by 10 km by 8 km which is next to the
10М на 10 км на 8 км который рядом с в
invasion line that you stormed there for a year
линии вторжения который вы год там
or 10 months Yes,
штурмовали или 10 месяцев штурмовали Да
and you didn’t take it, but bombed it, it’s
и вы его типа не взяли а разбомбили
just that no one was there  lives and is not
просто там никто не живёт и не
stationed
дислоцирующихся
nya You tell me the names of the
ня Вы скажите название
cities Damn, just like that, the king
городов Блин вот вот так прямо король
is sitting like that in front of the map Well now I
такой сидите перед картой Ну сейчас
’ll say that let’s
скажу что давайте
uh-huh I have a different question for now I’m
угу У меня вопрос другой пока Я сейчас
looking for everything here, it turns out that Bakhmut is
тут всё ищу получается вот то что бахмут
like, well, you consider this an
как бы ну вы же считаете это
insignificant advance as far as  I
незначительным продвижением насколько я
understand Correctly Well, it turns out you
понимаю Правильно Ну да получается вы
look, you covered 10 km in 10 months,
смотрите вы за 10 месяцев прошли 10 км
that’s all. Well, that is, for you, in fact, it’s
всё Ну вот то есть для вас по факту это
like,
как бы
on the scale of the Russian
ну в масштабах Российской
Federation, there was bakhmut and there is no bakhmut  yes
Федерации был бахмут и нету бахмута да
yes And we at this at this time while you are striking
да А мы в этот в это время пока вы бьёте
somewhere in Bakhmut destroy your army
где-то в бахмуте уничтожайте свою армию
there yes we are preparing strikes on St. Petersburg in
там да мы готовим удары по Питеру по
Tula super we are satisfied with this then
Туле супер нас этого устраивает дальше
what other cities strike then this yes strike then
какие ещё города удар то это да удар то
that’s all like this then what cities  Well, it’s
это всё как этому то какие города Ну вот
interesting,
интересно
well, listen, here, listen, there’s a
вот Ну слушай ну тут Слушай ну тут
big list, a
список большой
lot of Andreevka, some kind of it, there’s even
большо Андреевка какая-то он там даже
something else there, Andreevka Kato
есть что там ещё Андреевка Като
village, I have no idea. It’s near Bakhmut,
село Я понятия немею Это возле бахмута
and it looks like a village.
да походу село
Yes  Militopol
Да милитополь
Mito is the first
мито первые
city in general, Militopol is in the
д вобще город у ва милитополь это в
first days since you captured it, it’s not 2003,
первые дни с вы захватили это не 2003
but now we’re talking about 2003 or something.
год так А мы сейчас про 2003 год говорим
I’m talking about the last year.
что ли Я говорю за последний год
What is it now, the
Что
mighty Yandex for us? Now I
пого могучий Яндекс нам Сейчас никакой
don’t see any Andreevka in
Андреевки не вижу в
2023.  in the Lugansk region of Andreevka
2023 есть в Луганской области Андреевка
this is visible in the first
это видно в первые
days, and in 2023 Ukraine knocked out your
дни а Украина за 2023 год выбила ваши
landing ships Yes in
десантные корабли Да в
Crimea  airplane This is not an airplane This is already
Крыму самолёт Вот это не самолёт Это уже
in
в
202 Listen, well, there’s a bunch of Yes, there’s a bunch of those, a
202 Слушай ну тут Ках куча Да куча есть
bunch of them, call 2023, yes, the year, yes No,
те куча называй 2023 год да год да Нет
it’s not that it’s just there, it’s something that’s
оно не то что просто есть то что
been captured, that’s all, as it were, here Yes, yes, well,
захватили вот и всё как бы тут Да да ну
tell me, this is what you see  some
скажи ну вот какой ты видишь какие-то
big cities You have known friends there,
большие города У тебя же там знакомые на
but I mean, how do I
слуху есть а в смысле я откуда я знаю
know the big ones?
Ты знаешь он большой вот какой ещё
don’t listen, but what about
распиание не слушай а что вот так про
Bakhmut, that’s all, well, there was Bakhmut, yes and no,
бахмут то всё ну был бахмут вот да и нет
that’s all Yes, no, but there are strikes on
его всё Да нету но зато есть удары по
the territory of the Russian Federation, super
территории Российской Федерации супер
exchange So far, good Listen, Lisichansk is
размен Пока хороший Слушай а Лисичанск
criminal, so Lisichansk is also still the
криминально так Лисичанск - это тоже ещё
twenty-first year, this is the 2nd
двадцать вй год это дй
year of Svatov  Svatova, this is generally the first
год Сватова Сватова это вообще первый
first week of the war. That is, when you
первая неделя войны То есть вы когда вы
captured the damn thing. I’m discovering that it’s the
захватили блин Я открываю то что
twenty-third year, it shows everything. I
двадцать третий год он Всё показывает Я
don’t know where you got the information from,
не знаю откуда у вас информация такая
that I’m actually in the twenty-second year.  how
что двадцать второй год у мне вообще как
about Svatova, this is actually the first week, the
бу так Сватова это вообще первая неделя
Ukrainian army from the Lugansk region
украинская армия из Луганской области
howled
выла
a chance, too, for the second year,
чанс тоже д второй год
yes Avdeevka What is Avdeevka Dosya has not been
да Авдеевка Что такое а Авдеевка Дося не
taken
взята до сих
yet, so well, you are still good for 2 years
пор так ну и хороши за 2 года вы до сих
Avdeev Avdeevka Yes, from the line
пор Авдеев Авдеевка Да от линии
the invasion costs a couple  kilometers That is,
вторжение стоит пару километров То есть
you haven’t walked a couple of kilos in 2 years.
вы за 2 года не прошли пару
I have the feeling
кило У меня такое ощущение складывается
that damn it’s
что блин
like you haven’t squeezed anything out of us.
типа что что вы у нас ничего не отжали
Yes, that’s interesting, so read it. Well  cash you've
Да вот интересно так читай Ну нал ты уже
almost got a big list show me from this
почти большой список покажи мне из этого
list Well tell me which
списка Ну скажи какой
city so what's on your mind Tell me
город так А что тебя так парит Скажи по
you put it off no no Let's finish you were
ты отложил нет нет Давай добьём ты же
already flipping through the list you had the list in front of
листал уже у тебя же был список перед
your eyes You said here's a big
глазами Ты же сказал вот большой
list Well okay Look here  Anadol
список Ну окей Вот смотри анадоль
Andreevka Antonovka Barykina birch bark
Андреевка Антоновка Барыкина берестовое
it’s all, well, it’s all like 2022 when
это всё ну это всё типа 2022 год когда
they were captured
вот захватили
Farther and farther you were only
Всё дальше Всё дальше вас только
knocked out, they
выбивали
didn’t declare war
те войну не объявили войну
You declared war  not announced for you since
Вы во обяв война не объявлена у вас с
20 one
вой 20 один
you call for the twenty-second you call for the
го ты за двадцать второй называешь за
twenty-second you call I call
двадцать второй ты называешь называю то
what the list gave me And
что мня список выдал И всё
take it all look in Google or Yandex
ями возьми смотри в Google или в Яндекс
Bay list of settlements captured by the
Бей список населённые пункты захваченные
Russian Federation in the third year
Российской Федерацией в ть третьем году
come on all that  the same thing, the
давай гова всё то же самое вот всё то же
same thing is written, here I am reading the
самое написано вот я те читаю
list Lesnoye
список Лесное
Listvyanka Yes, these are all SL this is the 2nd year Minchik
Листвянка Да эти все сл это 2 год минчик
Maryanovka Melitopol Mirny Well
Марьяновка Мелитополь Мирный Ну
Melitopol Well, all this is the second year, the
Мелитополь Ну всё это д второй год
first weeks, everything is all you, that is, you
первые недели всё всё ты то есть ты
admit that in the twenty-third year you
признаёшь что в двадцать третьем году вы
couldn’t
не смогли ничего
take anything, and you’re also really
взять вть А тебе так же тебе так прямо
offended or something Yes, well, I’m interested, Well,
обидно что ли Да Ну вот мне интересно Ну
look, I’m just looking if you’re over twenty  the
смотри я просто смотрю если за двадцать
third year of you only In short, you say
третий год вас только Короче вы говорите
kana, that is, Russia was not able to
кана то есть Россия ничего не смогла
take anything in the twenty-third year Russia
взять за двадцать третий год Россия
got hit in the teeth and is now whining, uh,
получила по зубам и скулит теперь ээ
only in short Now it is also receiving on
только короче Теперь ещё получает по
its territory, yes it turns out yes Listen,
своей территории да получается да Слушай
well, if for you this territory was, well,
ну если для вас эта территория как бы ну
Yes
Да я особо не сказал
I didn’t say much I said everything We leaked you Oh, it’s just cooked, it’s just short, it’s a thrill, it’s just a thrill I love it so much when they open the SNP Ukraine to declare to Russia, yes, you wanted to get to London Yes, from there to the English Channel to Lvov Kyiv in 3 days and now take it you are glad that Ukraine somewhere there cannot take something back for you. So you, the Russian Federation for 2023, it turns out you can’t take anything, but you look at it and Ukraine  at this time, yes, it is
на это смотрите а Украина в это время да
already carrying out strikes on the territory of the
производит уже удары по территории
Russian Federation fully and there will be
Российской Федерации полноценно и будет
even
ещё
more Glory to Ukraine
больше Слава Украине
th Telegram right now the VN
й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
axis apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or to your ban and even
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people at the moment I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information  about streaming Tom in order for
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
us to write an operational link in Mali
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away and while there in  telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okrim video sche tezh tsikava korisna
окрим видео ще теж цикава корисна
information and we are guilty of you trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe E
подпишись E